(Raj:)It was a card for your 18th birthday.
Inside it said, "Happy birthday, Howard.
I love you. Dad."
Oh, and it was a "Far Side" card...
(Raj:)...the one where the frog has its tongue
stuck to the underside of an airplane.
(Raj:)Thinks it's a fly.
(Raj:)Silly frog. So funny.
Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)It was a map...
(Sheldon:)...leading to the lost treasure
of famous pirate "One-Eyed Willy."
(Howard:)Nice try. That's the plot for Goonies.
- Told you.
- Don't.
(Penny:)Amy?
(Amy:)You didn't know it...
(Amy:)...but your father was in the auditorium
at your high school graduation...
(Amy:)...and he cried
because he was so proud of you.
(Penny:)Really?
(Sheldon:)Or that's complete poppycock which Amy
made up. It still could be the map.